THE SUB-MAN
关注新浪微博
@FIX字幕侠
很好 很好
OK, that's right,
沿着边缘
along the edge.
好的 很好
Good. That's good.
别哄我了
Don't patronize me.
走几步路好什么好 太他妈平常了
Walking's not good. It's fuckin' normal.
我没有 罗伊先生 你做得很好
I'm not. That is good, Mr. Roy.
我要坐会儿
I need to sit down.
-椅子呢  -洛根
- Chair. - Logan,
如果你身体还没恢复好 去不了慈善晚宴
if you're not well enough for the charity dinner,
我可以跟这小帅哥一起去的
I maybe go with this handsome young man.
好了
OK. Now,
这个更难一点
this is a little trickier.
这是本体感受训练
This is the proprioception.
从一边到另一边
That's side to side.
把音乐关了 感觉像他妈在拍复建广告
Turn it off. It's like being inside a fuckin' commercial.
来吧
There you go.
你自己关掉
You turn it off yourself.
快来
Come on.
她特么要去哪儿
Where the fuck's she goin'?
翻译: 奶啾
翻译: 我的后面是猪精
翻译: 李木木
翻译: 这个家伙
翻译: 皮带断了
翻译: 宇宙万宝路
翻译: 海顿
翻译: 豆
时间轴: Heiforn
时间轴: 阿布
特效: 雨人
后期&压制: Jason肖
校对:渡渡
校对：宇宙万宝路
继     承
第 一 季  第４集
"无用的黄蜂陷阱"
监制: 宇宙万宝路
谢谢
Thank you.
拉瓦 你决定好明晚的事了吗
Rava, hey, did you decide yet about tomorrow night?
对我来说还挺重要的
It's kind of a big night for me.
我要为爸的罗伊慈善晚宴致辞
I'm making Dad's RECNY ball speech.
我以为你的"但愿可以"就是"可以"的意思
I just kind of assumed your "Hopefully" was a "Yes."
当真的吗
Are you serious?
...GDP指数显示美国经济
...GDP numbers that showed the US economy
增长态势喜人
maintained a brisk pace of growth
年增长率为2.8%
at a 2.8% annual rate.
-洛杉矶怎么样  -挺好的
- How was L.A.? - Great.
都他妈是一群疯子 但挺好的
They're all fuckin' nuts, but great.
你能联系兰斯润色下我的讲稿吗
Can you get onto Lance about my speech?
去夜谈节目弄几个写手来
And can we get one of the late night guys to,
-替我编场段子啥的  -段子
- you know, cook me up a bit? - A bit?
对 段子 就是即兴笑话大合集
Yeah, a bit. You know, a selection of jokes and riffs?
你要讲笑话吗
You're gonna do a joke?
瞧你这话问的 朕乃冷嘲热讽之王
What does that mean? I was fuckin' king of the Lampoon.
狠狠嘲讽他们的份额
Kicked their distribution into shape.
-我取消了你早上所有的行程 因为...  -谁在我爸的...
- I cleared your morning because... - Who's that in my dad's...?
因为你爸要见你
because your dad wants to see you.
看样子你不知道这回事
Guessing you didn't know that.
我不知道 但是...
No, I didn't know. But, uh...
这算好消息 对吧
it's great news. Right?
-你知道吗  -不知道 但挺好的
- Did you know? - No, but it's great.
当然 当然
Sure. Oh, sure.
他不该提前告诉你吗
Shouldn't he have told you?
好吧 听着 我会...
OK, uh, listen, I'll just, um...
收拾一下
get myself straight
去看望咱的老... 领头羊
and go and see the old... fuckin' goat.
好的
Ok.
你真帅
You look good.
是啊 谢谢
Uh, well, yeah. Well, thank you.
糟糕 格蕾丝...
Whoops. Uh, Grace, um...
瞧 这就是你待在这里也没用的原因
OK, see, this is why your staying here doesn't work.
家里明明有五个洗手间 你却在这儿
There are five bathrooms in this place, and you're here.
你在这儿干嘛 就好比 我现在想放屁 但我放不出来
Why are you here? Like, right now I have to fart, and I'm not.
-我放不出来就因为你在这儿  -好吧
- I'm physically not farting because you're here. - OK.
我只是觉得有点放不开 成不
I'm just feeling a little oppressed is all, OK?
谢谢你
Thank you.
需要我跟康纳说一下 然后确认座次安排吗
Do you want me to speak to Connor and confirm table arrangements?
-随便  -今年办的规模跟去年的差不多
- Uh-huh. - We're hosting basically the same as last year,
就多了乔伊丝和丹尼尔 这样行吗
plus Joyce and Daniel. Is that OK?
小西 去年我没去
I didn't go last year, Shiv.
你去了的
Yes, you did.
还记得去年那个高盛集团的种族歧视的比利时人吗
Remember we had that racist Belgian GS guy?
就老婆想自杀那个
And his wife who wanted to kill herself?
西沃恩 你觉得我会不记得
Siobhan, I think I would remember
我们一起参加的首场"纽约创意展演暨罗伊家族慈善晚宴"吗
our first Roy Endowment Creative New York ball together.
我当时还在香港 开发主题公园
I was trapped in Honk Kong, scoping out theme parks.
-真的吗  -真的 亲爱的
- Really? - Yeah. Honey,
我可是看着我妈的"名利场"杂志里的
growing up I used to look at the pictures of the RECNY
罗伊慈善晚宴图片长大的
in Mom's "Vanity Fairs."
然而现在 当年那个圣保罗的小男孩
And now, a little boy from St. Paul's going,
要和世上最美的姑娘去参加晚宴了
with the most beautiful gal in the world.
-搞什么鬼  -怎么了
- Oh, what the fuck? - What?
好一张终生难忘的妙图啊 不是吗
It's quite a haunting image, isn't it?
那只"眼"好像能追着你满屋子跑了
The eye almost seems to follow you around the room.
什么情况
What is this?
你的客户 未来的参议员 很显然
You know, your client, the future senator? Apparently,
这是她老公的屁眼
this is her husband's asshole.
什么 滚蛋 你能证明吗
What? Fuck off. Can you prove that?
他自己发出去的 还加了个标题"看本大爷的屁眼"
He posted it himself with the caption: "Check out my asshole."
挂在"肮脏的富人"网上
It was on a site called Filthy Rich.
-大家都有了吗  -目前为止 只有咱们有
- Has everybody got it? - Just us, I believe, right now.
被泄露给了泛美 我的小伙伴觉得我会感兴趣
Leaked to ATN. My buddy thought I'd be intrigued.
好啊 放马过来吧
All right, well, bring it on.
真刚烈啊
Ooh, feisty.
干嘛 他们不播报吗
What, they're not gonna run it?
这很下流 很诡异
It's dirty, it's weird,
而且正好是那种
and it's evidence of precisely the kind
令人作呕的自由主义进洞之爱
of disgusting liberal metro butt-love
足以让我们这群看客气到买止吐药
that makes our viewership angry enough to buy pharmaceuticals.
-行啊 非常敢射你  -好啊
- Oh, OK, fuck you very much. - OK, well,
真不想当传噩耗的坏人
hate to be the bearer of bad news.
怎么称呼那东西 "他身上的某处私密部位"吗
What do we call it, "An intimate part of his body"?
别 听起来像是他的小兄弟
No! That sounds like his dick.
或者是他的"菊花"
Or just his "Anus"?
"菊花" 在早餐时间提吗
"Anus"? At breakfast?
太他妈恶心了
That's a fucking juice-dropper.
"他身上某个极其隐私的部位"
"A very private part of his body."
太没新意了 她有点睡眠不足
It's boring. And she needs to get more sleep.
-卡伦  -怎么了
- Karen. - Yeah?
-你睡得还好吗  -我觉得挺好
- You sleepin' OK? - I thought so.
是吗 你趴着睡吗
Yeah? Are you sleeping on your face?
-诶呦  -开个玩笑而已
- Boom! Ouch. - I'm just kidding.
-你看起来很好  -亲爱的 我怎么样
- You look great. - How about me, darling?
我看起来如何
How do I look?
忍操脸 马克 忍一忍还是能操的脸
FIE, Mark. Fuckable in an emergency.
如果咱们都不叫上这个冷淡的小骗子
Now, if we don't call out this frigid little phony,
那谁来
who will?
好 挺好
Yeah. Good.
老爹
Hey, Dad.
我都不知道你来了
I didn't know you were coming in.
格丽知道吗
Did-- Did Gerri?
我还需要你批准吗
Do I need permission?
拜托 别这么臭屁
Hey, come on. Screw you.
我只想确保你不会
Just making sure you're not selling
在我不知情的情况下卖掉更多公司股份
any more of the company from under me.
你想参与进来吗
Oh, you want to get into that?
是你欠了一屁股债
You know, you put a hole in us
给我们挖了个天坑
by taking on a shitload of debt.
不过 听着 这...
But look, this is, uh...
很开心见到你
it's great to see you.
你确定自己没事吗
Are you sure you're OK?
也许你应该先听听简报 休息下 好吗
Maybe you should get a briefing and get some rest, yeah?
好啊
Yeah, OK.
约瑟夫
Joseph!
把轮椅推过来 我要去小便
Bring the wheelchair! I need to take a leak!
那啥 老爸回来了
Hey. So, uh, Dad's back.
回哪 回到办公室吗
Back where? Back in the chair?
有点快啊 是吧
Seems kind of fast, right?
但是很显然 这样很好
But, you know, it's good, obviously.
他的脑仁从后脑勺掉下来时候 你才会开心吧
You'd love it if his brain fell out the back of his head.
老天 我只是担心万一...
Jesus. I'm just scared in case...
你只是担心 万一他把你踢出局
You're scared in case he tries to push you out
扼杀你的种种计划 比如优步上播新闻 脸书上晒猫
and your plans for, you know, Uber for news and Facebook for cats
和广纳建言的办公室
and open plan office.
你需要一个舞台把你的想法撸进...
You want a dance platform jerkin' off idea gloop into...
脑子里
think boxes.
我得挂电话了
I gotta go.
-罗曼 早上好  -弗兰克
- Roman. Good morning. - Frank.
不 纠正一下 从我的角度来看 这并不是个"好"的早上
No, correction, it is not a good morning from my POV
因为你出现了 而我他妈讨厌你
because you're here and I fuckin' hate you.
拜托 小家伙
Oh, come on, kid.
到底他妈的怎么回事
What the fuck is goin' on?
你老爸让我回来的
Your dad asked me to come back.
真是他妈的"鼬鼠的胜利"
Oh, the fuckin'-- the weasel prevails.
这名字挺适合做你自传的标题的
That'd be a good name for your autobiography,
如果有混蛋写这本书的话
if they did books by jerks.
天啦 你真是可悲
God, you're pathetic.
-他道歉了  -当然 伙计 当然会道歉
- He apologized. - Sure, man. Yeah.
他开车撞我们的互惠生的时候可没有道歉
He didn't apologize when he hit our au pair with his car.
他想让我给你指点迷津
He wants me to show you the ropes.
"是她的错 谁让她长这么矮" 他这么说的
"It was her fault for being too short," He said.
好吧
Ok.
-没别的了吗  -你什么意思
- Nothing else? - What do you mean?
我的意思是 考虑到发生的事情
I mean, in terms of what went up there.
因为刚开始还是手指 然后是拳头
Because first it's a finger, then it's a fist.
最后是一个像理查德·尼克松的假阴茎
then it's a dildo shaped like Richard Nixon.
操蛋
Ohh. Fuck this!
男人就不会收到这个
A man wouldn't be getting this.
我们就用这句
Let's say that.
好 同意 百分百同意
Yeah, agreed. Hundred percent.
但是 对我们来说 目前
But for us, now,
这问题不会消失
this isn't gonna go away,
所以我们得弄清楚 知道细节
so we need to be clear, we need to know the details.
我觉得你应该再和你丈夫谈谈
I think you need to talk to your husband again.
问题不会消失 是因为泛美不让它消失
It's not going away because ATN won't let it go away.
所以我觉得你应该再和你父亲谈谈
So I think you should talk to your father.
我只是希望座位图能有用
I just hope the seating plan holds.
如果有用...
If it does...
小心了 中东
look out, Middle East,
因为我会修补一切
'cause I can fix anything.
我只是希望你们知道
I just want you to know
你们是我有幸一起共事过的
you're the best damn bunch of people
最好的一群人
I ever had the honor to work for.
非常感谢你们
Thank you very much.
他来了
Here he comes.
比尔 有史以来最好的老板
Bill. The best boss that ever lived.
就像曼德拉操了圣诞老人 然后生下了比尔一样
It's like Mandela fucked Santa and gave birth to Bill.
谢谢大家
Thank you, everybody.
你听说洛根的事了吗
Did you hear about Logan?
他们说他回来了
They say he came in.
当然 我知道
Uh, uh-huh. Yeah, I knew.
但是我不能说
But I couldn't say.
谢谢
Thank you.
非常感谢你们
Thank you so much.
快点啦 你个和蔼的老混球
Come on, you genial old fucker.
快到这里来 我可不想等到天荒地老
Get in here already, before it's time for me to retire.
-比尔  -不好意思啊
- Hey, Bill! - Sorry about all that.
没什么啦 比尔 我也希望有一天
No problem, Bill! I just hope one day
我也能像你一样备受尊重
I can eventually inspire similar affection.
这位
Uh, this is,
这位是格雷格
this is Greg,
我入驻办公室时招入麾下的新人
new kid I took under my wing when I started.
其实我是家族一员...
I'm actually a part of the fam...
不用讲你的人生故事了 格雷格
Doesn't need to hear your life story, Greg.
-谢谢你所做的一切  -不客气
- So, uh, thanks for everything. - No.
不过 在我拍最后的大合照之前
But listen, before I do the final photo,
有件事... 我得跟你说一下
there's a... thing I need to mention.
-好啊  -我们俩单独聊
- Cool. - You know, just us?
好吧 当然
Oh. Yeah. Yeah.
-很高兴见到你  -谢谢你的理解
- Great to meet you. - Yeah. Thanks for understanding.
-谢谢你 比尔  -不客气
- Thank you, Bill. - You're welcome.
好了 是这么回事...
OK. So, uh...
我已经把无线网络关了 然后...
I've turned off the Wi-Fi, and...
这台电脑... 跟网络和联网计算机是完全隔离的
this is, uh... this is air-gapped,
我要做个文档给你
so I'm gonna create a Word document for you,
然后我打印给你 因为我不想
and then I'm gonna print it, because I don't want
任何纸质材料上留有我的笔迹
anything with my handwriting on it.
你是不是退休以后
I think someone has been watching
看了太多间谍电影啊 比尔
a few too many spy movies since they retired, eh, Bill?
没错 有可能吧
Yeah, maybe.
在这
Ah. Here.
这是存储处存储的
This, uh, this is the number
一组存储文件的编号
of a set of storage files in the depository,
主题是
and the subject is, well,
某种... 这不是什么大事
something that... it's not a big deal,
但是需要处理下
but it needs to be handled,
而且... 你是家族的人
and, uh... you're in the family.
...这是法律办公室的名字
So... this is the name of the legal office
这是对应的中介机构
that is the intermediary,
这是公司外面的人
and this is the person outside the firm
我们拿他们做防火墙
that we've been using as a firewall
用来处理保密协定方面的麻烦
to deal with the blowback from the NDAs.
这不是什么大事 汤姆
It's not a big deal, Tom.
这到底是什么 比尔
Right, but what is it, Bill?
这个...
Well...
你... 你有两个可行的选择
You...you have two viable options.
我可以告诉你一切 完全没问题
I can tell you everything, and that's fine.
我也可以不告诉你... 你就不会知道
Or I can not tell you, and... you wouldn't know,
这样你就可以避开整个死亡深渊
and then you can steer clear of the whole death pit.
那样也没问题
And that would be fine, too.
所以
So, I mean,
好消息是 不管你怎么选 一切都没问题的
the nice news is, either way, both ways, everything is fine.
只要低温保存核燃料棒 就不会有东西爆炸
Just keep the nuclear rods cool, nothing's gonna blow.
所以... 不仅有一个死亡深渊
OK, so...there's the death pit,
在死亡深渊的底部 还有一根核燃料棒
and at the bottom of the death pit there's nuclear rods?
这个嘛...
Well...
你现在能告诉我好消息了吗 比尔
You want to give me the good news now, Bill?
抱歉
Excuse me.
-摄影师准备好了  -棒呆了
- Photographer's ready. - Terrific!
谢谢 凯莉
Thanks, Kelly.
好了...
And...
打印
print.
你得告诉老爸 让他别插手
OK, you need to tell Dad to back the fuck off.
你现在不该已经到1OAK夜店了吗
Hey, shouldn't you be at 1 OAK or something by now?
你知道他聘回弗兰克来看管我吗
You know he rehired Frank to babysit me?
我不需要保姆
I don't need a babysitter.
好吗 尤其是不能操的那种
OK? Especially one I don't get to fuck.
-你认真的吗  -非常认真
- Seriously?  - Yes.
-弗兰克回来了  -是的 拜托 你才是总裁
- Frank is back?  - Yeah. I mean, you're CEO.
他有权力这么做吗
Can he even do that?
我不...
I don't...
这... 值得商榷
It's... It's a question.
好吧 行 跟他谈谈
OK, well, have a talk with him,
让他少管闲事
tell him to butt out,
现在大局掌握在我们手里
because we are running the show now.
告诉他回病床上歇着
Tell him he needs to go back to bed
喝点汤 好好休息
and eat some soup, get some rest.
听着 别紧张 行吗
Look, relax, OK?
你知道
The, uh, you know,
大恐龙在被流星砸死之前
the dinosaur is having one last roar at the meteor
会发出最后的吼叫 但是 你瞧
before it wipes him out. But look,
...你已经做得很好了
...you're doing a great job.
谢谢你 谢谢 老哥
Thank you. Thanks, man.
能听到你这么讲真好 任务艰巨
It's actually good to hear. It's a big job.
了解 老弟 还用说吗
I know it, bro. Tell me about it.
你需要帮助吗 我可以帮你
Do you want some help? I can help you,
我们能在老爸"无用的黄蜂陷阱"的演讲上联手搞点事
we can tag-team it on Dad's speech at Sad Sack Wasp Trap.
应该可以吧
Um, I guess, yeah,
毕竟是总裁该做的
I mean, it is a CEO thing,
那我就把整个流程准备好
so, I mean, like I have a whole thing prepared
-讲点笑话 然后... -你还会讲笑话
- with jokes, and so...  - You're doing jokes?
为啥大家都要质疑我 我很有幽默感的
Why does everyone keep saying that? I'm funny.
是呢 你肯定能秒杀全场
Yup. I'm sure you're gonna kill it.
-你打算带谁去  -就我一个 拉瓦很忙
- Who you taking? - Uh, no one. Rava's busy.
-她不想去吧 了解  -所以我可能要唱独角戏了
- Doesn't want to? Got it. - So maybe I'll roll solo.
那画面多难看
How's that gonna look?
堂堂总裁去晚宴竟连个丑姑娘都带不过来
CEO can't even get an ugly sister to go to the ball?
-你知道我想邀请谁吗  -谁
- You know who I'd like to take?  - Hmm?
安娜·纽曼 泛美那边的金发妞
Anna Newman. That blonde chick from ATN?
金发... 对 我即刻就想上了她
The bl... Oh, shit, yeah! I'd fuck that in a minute.
-带她去  -不大好吧 毕竟我是她老板
- Take her. - It's not cool. I'm her boss.
拉倒吧 你这个可怜兮兮的臭娘炮
Oh, come on, what a pathetic beta-cuck.
"不好意思 请问一下 这样做好吗
"Uh, excuse me, uh, would it be cool,
因为我的裤裆里不是很舒服
'cause I have something very secret in my pants.
我可以把它掏出来吗 拜托了 还是说这个话题很敏感"
Would it be OK to show, please? Or is that a trigger warning?"
我的天呐 罗曼 你他妈就是行走的官司
Jesus, Roman, you're a walking fuckin' lawsuit.
才不是 我很诚实 会直接说
Uh, no, I'm honest, I'm just like,
"你好啊 我喜欢你的脸蛋 我想操你的脸蛋
"Hey, I like your face. I wanna fuck your face.
可以射你脸上吗"
Can I cum on your face?"
这就是我被妞淹没的秘诀
Which is why my face is drowning in pussy
而你连自己老婆都碰不到
and you're not even fucking your wife.
太扎心了 对不起 只是...
Too far. Eeh! Sorry, it just...
这就是事实
them's the facts.
... 不用了 谢谢
... No, thank you!
请别来打搅我 谢谢了
Please leave me alone, please! Thank you!
我... 我能行
I... I got it.
早上好
Morning.
好吧 扶我一下
OK. Give me a hand. Yeah.
先说私事
Uh, personal first,
然后说公司
then the corporal.
公事
Corporate.
好吧
Um, OK.
好的 私事没别的
Well, personal, nothing much.
晚宴前的部分
Pre-ball piece,
捐款接收人的档案
profiles of endowment recipients,
都进行得很顺利
that's all great,
还有一条关于您健康的消息
and just a little piece on your health,
但我认为您没必要听这个
but I don't think you need to hear that.
直说
Say it.
"肯德尔·罗伊将在今晚的罗伊慈善晚宴上
Um, "Kendall Roy will give the traditional address
例行致辞
at the RECNY charity ball tonight,
这表示即便已经从中风中痊愈过来
in a sign that even after recovery from his stroke,
洛根·罗伊也将从公事中退位让贤"
Logan Roy is intending to wind down from public duties."
他从哪儿得到这消息的 谁跟他说的
Where did he get that? Who gave him that?
-我... 我不知道  -那我给你个建议 查出来
- I... I don't know.  - Well, here's an idea: find out.
不然就滚蛋再去找一个每年付你一百万美金的冤大头
Or find some other prick to pay ya a million a fuckin' year.
知道了
Ok.
我得告诉你 负责晚宴这件事
I just gotta tell you, handling the ball,
对我毫无压力
it's just not a big deal for me,
这真的太好了
which is the thing that's so nice.
-没什么难的  -"退位让贤"
- It is not a big deal. - "Winding down."
退你妈呢 我还要往上爬
Winding fucking down. I'm winding up.
主管一切 真的挺搞笑的
It's just funny, being in charge.
我记得很多年前
I remember years ago
我在饭桌上坐在你和老妈之间
I'd be at the table between you and Mom
我们往下看 看到了市长
and we'd look down, and there'd be the mayor,
和过去纽约的风云人物
and all the names of old New York,
你凑近我的耳朵说
and you'd whisper in my ear, you'd say,
"阿斯特已经习惯了 他会一直操盘直到
"That Astor used to be that, and he ran this
把一切都搞砸
till he SNAFUed that,
他还跟她鬼混 她就是个贱人
and he's porking her, and she's a slut."
那简直... 是段太温馨的时光了
And it was just... A very lovely time.
是啊
Yeah.
你母亲享受这一切
Your mom loved all that.
... 该死的黄蜂陷阱
... Fuckin' Wasp Trap.
你怎么想关于我
What would you think about
部分接管慈善基金的事
me taking over a little on the foundation?
我们能暂且从生病的孩子们和当代舞蹈中抽身
Could we pivot it away from sick kids and contemporary dance
去考虑一下税务改革吗
and toward tax reform?
-什么  -恕我直言 不管怎样人们都会跳舞
- Huh? - To be frank, everyone's dancing anyway,
慈善也多得很
and there are a lot of charities
虽然全都无用... 我确实喜欢这些
that cater to sad sacks... God knows I love 'em,
但是 为什么不致力于促进企业解放呢
but hey, what about lending a hand to stimulate free enterprise?
行吧 我们... 我们先看看今晚的情况 行吗
Yeah, well, let's... let's see how tonight goes, huh?
好
Yeah.
我可没时间搞这出
I don't have time for this shit.
-你好  -你好
- Hey.  - Hi.
那个... 听着
Uh, so... look,
我想劝你收手
I want you to call off your dogs.
然后呢
Mm-hmm.
因为这么对乔伊丝穷追不舍
Because this obsession with Joyce,
实在是... 太过火了
it's... it's out of line.
在你的半小时新闻播报里 关注度太高了
It's sitting very high on your half hour.
继续
Uh-huh.
而且是报复性的
And it's vindictive.
而且实际上 这不利于民主
And actually, it's bad for democracy.
你不做出点回应吗
Are you going to respond?
我认为我们得牢记
Well, I think it's important to remember
我并不是给自己屁眼拍照的那个人
that I'm not the one taking pictures of my asshole here.
的确
Yeah.
你是觉得我爸喜欢这玩意才播报它的吗
Are you running this because you think my dad likes this shit?
他可不会给他的人施那么大的压力
Oh, he wouldn't put that kind of pressure on his people.
行吧
Ok.
那如果我能
Look, if I could get some
从别人身上挖到点新闻
nasty little tidbits on some other folk,
你们能停手吗
could you ramp this down?
不只有我们在搞这个 小西
We're not the only ones running it, Shiv.
全天下都知道这个故事
It's a hugely popular story.
没错 但你带领着他们 伊娃
Yeah, but you're leading it, Eva.
你在一个新闻频道上
You had a ten-minute "Sexpert" Segment
用十分钟的"性爱专家"部分
on "How to keep your man happy in bed,"
探讨"怎样在床上满足你的男人"
on a news channel.
行 你已经表达得很清楚了...
OK, you've said your piece, so...
我也听得很清楚了
and I've listened.
-好的  -好的
- Great.  - Great.
实际上 不行 你知道吗
Actually, no. You know what?
我作为她的参谋必须得说 这种程度的攻击
I'm saying as her strategist, this level of attack
会开始影响你的专业判断
begins to reflect on your professional judgement.
并且你需要思考一下未来 因为这...
And you need to think about the future, because this...
这已经是旧世界了
this is the old world,
总有一天 这个世道会变的
and someday, in this world, things will change.
我不允许任何其他战略家出现在这栋楼
You know I wouldn't let any other strategist in the building,
除了这一层
let alone this floor.
是吗 感激不尽
Well, I am very grateful.
既然提到专业判断
So when we're talking professional judgement,
你最好牢记 你能在这里
good to bear in mind that you're only here
只是因为你的姓和大楼上刻的那个一样
because your name matches the one carved on the building.
最后一件事
OK, last thing.
面对媒体
For the press and comms,
一定要宣称我才是总裁
it's clear, right, that I'm CEO.
但我们盼望父亲的回归 至于何时我们也不知道
We hope one day my dad will be back, we don't know when.
谢谢大伙 谢谢
Thank you. Thanks, guys.
肯德尔 斯图伊来了
Hey, Kendall. Stewy's here.
我让他在南厢等着
I just put him in the South Tank
以防你不想见他
in case you want to keep it on the DL.
肯德尔 能占用你一会时间吗
Hey, Kendall. Can I grab five?
可以
Uh-huh.
有点事
Um, there's something, uh,
有点事你不知情
something that you don't know about,
这事说不定
and maybe it's probably
你也不想知情
something that you don't want to know about.
而且...
And, uh...
你知道我爸常说的一句话吗
You know what my dad always said?
他说他爱护所有员工
He'd say he loved all his employees,
但尤其喜欢那些
but he particularly loved the guys
为他默默吃屎背锅的人
who ate the shit for him and he never even knew it.
懂了
Got it.
懂了 我准备刀叉和荷兰酱的时候
Got it. Excuse me while I get myself a knife and a fork
就不好意思了
and some Hollandaise.
-来了  -来了 哥们
- Hey! - Hey, bro.
还顺利吗
How's it goin'?
-顺利啊 怎么了  -你爹回来了吗
- Good. What's up? - So your dad's in?
是 他自己回来了
Yup, he made it in.
这让我们都很开心
Which we were all, uh, delighted about.
-你们开心吗  -当然了
- You were delighted about? - Sure.
当然 怎么回事
Sure. What's the story?
没什么 他可厉害了
No, he's great, you know,
他想提醒我们他还活着
he likes to remind us he's still alive.
有他管着很好 可他需要多休养
It's great to get his take, but he needs a lot of rest.
-老爸 我们正说你呢  -罗伊先生 洛根
- Dad. Hey. Just talkin' about you. - Sir Roy. Logan.
很高兴见到您 您近况如何
It's just great to see you. How have you been?
你就是那个占了我大部分资产的蠢货
So, you're the little schmuck who owns such a big chunk of me.
老爸 这是斯图伊 你们见过无数次了
Dad, it's Stewy. You guys have met like a million times.
恕我打搅了
Excuse me barging in,
但是格丽说我稍后要和奥普勒公司开会...
it's just Gerri told me I have a meeting with Opalite later...
就为说一句"我喜欢 我买了"
just to say, "I like it. Buy it."
-好吗 肯  -很好的想法
- OK, Ken? - OK, good thought.
我一会找您商量
Uh, I'll come find you and we can discuss.
行 但我要是见不到你 我就要它了
Sure, but if I don't see you, I want it.
好的...
OK, uh...
其实这不一定是最好的行业选择
Well, it's not necessarily the best option in the sector,
所以 但我们能...
so, uh, so, yeah, but we can, uh...
我想进军数据挖掘 收购它
I want us into data mining. Buy it.
这个行业太泛滥了 好吗
It's a really flooded sector, OK?
全是骗子和废物
Lotta hustlers, lots of bullshit.
就跟淘金热似的
You know, it's a gold rush.
是啊 没错
Oh, yeah.
谁想要金子呢
And who wants gold?
给他们一个令之心动的出价
Make them an offer they get excited about.
一个能让他们在晚上向老婆炫耀的出价
Make them an offer they want to tell their wives about at night.
好一个性别歧视 老爸
Nice outdated sexism, Dad,
不过我确定你心思全放这上边了
but I'm sure you're all over the data mining.
你说什么
I'm sorry?
你还好吗 老爸
You OK? Dad?
要我... 叫人吗
Hey, should I get... someone?
也许你该回家了 好吗
Maybe you should go home. Yeah?
我只是... 想尿尿
I just, uh... need to piss.
好的
Ok.
很好 谢谢你的坦诚 老家伙
Great. Well, thanks for sharing, uh, old guy.
-很高兴他去撒尿了  -抱歉
- Glad he's gonna go piss. - Uh, sorry. You know.
他还在恢复
He's still recovering.
我问你 严格来讲
Listen, just technically,
我不想扫兴 小肯
and I don't want to sound reductive, Ken,
但... 现在到底谁掌权
but... who's in charge right now?
我 我掌权
Me. I am.
法定和实际也是我
Legally and effectively.
好的 瑞克 谢谢你帮忙
OK, Rick, thanks for that.
谢谢
Thank you.
受益良多 谢谢
Very useful. Thanks.
去你丫的
Fuck off.
格雷格... 听着
So, Greg, uh... listen.
我刚与我的私人律师谈过
I just had a meeting with my private attorney,
貌似我被扔到病毒堆里了
it seems I have been exposed to a virus.
是吗
Oh. Right.
是
Yeah.
坐
Sit down.
这病毒很致命
It's a deadly virus.
现在... 我完蛋了
and now... now I'm fucked!
一辈子完蛋了
Forever.
-听起来很糟糕  -是很糟糕
- It sounds bad. - It is bad.
我好像需要说出来
It is. And, uh, I kind of need to share it.
但我说给谁听...
But anyone I talk to, uh...
我说给谁听 就会杀了谁
anyone I talk to, I effectively kill.
给
Here.
这是个死人坑 格雷格
That's the death pit, Greg.
你看看
Take a look.
我觉得... 我不太想在死人坑里待着
I... I mean, I feel like I might not like it in the death pit.
看看吧
Go ahead.
我们是一家人
You're family.
谢谢
Thank you.
-这太复杂了  -有点 但不是太复杂
- It's complicated. - Kind of, yeah. But not really.
多年来 在邮轮公司有个不成文的政策
For a number of years there was an unofficial company policy
如果发生了严重犯罪事件
on the cruise lines that if there was a serious criminal incident
就尽可能不要返航
we would, if possible, sail, not home,
而要去加勒比或是南美的港口
but to a Caribbean or South American port
那里有所谓的"友好"政府
where there were so-called "Friendly" Authorities,
可以大事化小 避免消极公关
and we could minimize the incident to avoid negative PR.
-犯罪事件是...  -偷窃 性侵
- Incidents like-- - Theft. Sexual assault.
强奸 谋杀
Rape. Murder.
好吧 很恶劣
OK. The bad ones.
没错 这里有数百起
Yeah. There's hundreds in there.
邮轮的船长 莱斯特
You know, the head of cruises himself, Lester,
会参加这些娱乐旅行
would go on these entertainment tours,
会见舞者
meeting the dancers,
与那些愿意跟他上床的人续约
and extending the contracts of the ones that would suck him off.
每查到一个人 我们就得用钱堵她的嘴
Everyone we could, we paid off, we hushed up.
但邮件和通信
But there are emails,
全是连锁反应... 而且要炸了
there's correspondence... it's ready to blow.
这他妈是个定时炸弹
It's a fucking time bomb.
那你... 你想怎么做
So, what are you... what are you gonna do?
我不知道 不知道
I don't know! I don't know!
因为我寻求建议的每一个都成了知情人
Because anyone I ask for advice, I make complicit.
如果你知道这些员工是谁 就应该讲出来
If you know about this stuff, you should tell.
但你不能这么做 因为这是在扩散病毒
But you can't, because you're gonna spread the virus.
那...
So...
我也被感染了 是吗
I have the virus, don't I?
肯...
OK, Ken, uh...
你去把奥普勒公司的资料拿过来
why don't you grab the Opalite material?
我解释过了 老爸
Uh, well, as I explained, Dad,
他们就像卖丹药的江湖郎中 懂吗
I think they're kind of snake oil salesmen, you know?
比如你买了一台冰箱以后
Like they're the people who you buy a refrigerator
他们的算法就能给你推送
and their algorithm is sending you, like,
三十条冰箱广告 强大的算法
30 ads for more fridges. Great algo.
反正你这个商业天才把我出卖给了那位蠢货
Well, you're the business genius who sold me out to this fucker,
所以我很想听斯图尔特的想法
so I'd like to hear Stewart's thoughts.
好的 我去找杰西...
OK, I'll get Jess to...
你他妈走出去只需要三十秒 孩子
It's a 30-fuckin'-second walkaway, son.
好
Sure.
那么 斯图尔特...
So, Stewart...
杰西
Jess.
怎么了 杰西
Hey, Jess?
什么
Yeah?
是不是有人...
Has anyone been...
你父亲进来待了两分钟
Uh, your dad came in for like two minutes.
什么...
What the...
老天啊 我操
Oh, Jesus, fuck.
就像进了...
Just like gone in...
来了
Hey.
咱们应该会买下来
So, I think we're buyin'.
你同意吗 斯图尔特
Good with you, Stewart?
您是老板
You're the boss.
没问题吧
All good?
斯图尔特 今晚你要去那个无用的黄蜂陷阱吗
Stewart, are you goin' to the Sad Sack Wasp Trap tonight?
-什么...  -他指的是罗伊慈善晚宴
-The... - He means the RECNY ball.
对 我要去 很抱歉听说您去不了
Oh. Yes. I am. I'm sorry to hear that you're not gonna make it.
不是的 我会去的
Oh, no, no, I'll be there.
毕竟是我给这破晚会掏腰包
Well, I'm payin' for the fuckin' thing,
所以我最好去咯
so I might as well go.
是啊
Yeah.
你确定是他吗
You sure it was him?
你觉得有很多人进来这里撒尿吗
You think a lot of people come in here and take a piss?
可能有人洒了什么
Maybe someone spilled something.
是啊 可能我他妈忘了这有块
Yeah, maybe the massive fucking ice sculpture
巨型冰雕融化了 这就是尿
I forgot about melted. It's urine.
假旗行动: 使用其他组织的旗帜 制服等手段误导公众
这不是假旗行动吧
This isn't a false flag, is it?
是你自己在地板上撒的吧
Did you piss on your own floor?
你干嘛那个表情 万一... 别人知道怎么办
Why are you looking like that? What... What if people knew?
-格丽 你得跟他谈谈  -你想要我说什么
- Gerri, you gotta talk to him. - What do you want me to say?
首先告诉他去哪里撒尿拉屎
Well, first tell him where to go pee-pee and poo-poo.
他进来 然后和斯图伊谈话
He came in, he was talking to Stewy.
之后他要做什么 射在我咖啡里吗
What's he gonna do next, start jizzing in my coffee?
在我平板上大号吗
Take a dump on my iPad?
他还在恢复状态
He's still in recovery mode.
如果他觉得自己有能力回公司
If he thinks he's OK to come back,
那就应该告诉你和格丽
he should talk to you, Gerri,
还有提名委员会 选个日期 对吧
and the nominating committee, and set a date. Right?
严格来讲是 这算是灰色地带 因为...
Well, technically, but it's kind of a gray area because...
-他说他今晚要去  -你开玩笑吧
- He says he's coming tonight. - You're kidding.
好的 这就需要担心了 因为很显然
OK, well, that's a concern, because obviously
主要投资人及媒体都在场...
with major investors and press on hand..
是啊 我知道 如果他失控怎么办
Yeah, I know. What if he freaks out?
如果他在汤里睡着怎么办
What if he falls asleep in his soup?
如果他叫嚣种族歧视言论怎么办
What if he starts shouting racist comments?
那不就是平常的夜晚吗 宝贝
Just another Saturday night, baby.
信托责任: 企业管理层要全心全意为股东利益而运作企业资产的责任
我们有信托责任不让公司看起来 这么疯癫
We have a fiduciary duty not to let the company look, uh, nuts.
当你发现他这么做了以后 你又做了什么 肯德尔
What did you do, Kendall, when you realized he'd done this?
-我做了什么  -对 你做出了什么回应
- What did I do? - Yeah. How did you respond?
我不知道 我可不想羞辱他
I-- I don't know, I didn't want to humiliate him.
怎么了
What?
这是我这个月第三次给你注射
This would be the third injection I've given you in a month.
他觉得自己务必到场
He feels he needs to be there.
你本来一年只能注射三次
You're only meant to have three in a year.
难怪你失眠
No wonder you're not sleeping.
你正冒着长期精神受损的风险
You're risking long-term nerve damage.
注射 别逼逼
Jab. Not jabber.
闭嘴 然后注射
Shut up and shoot up.
亲爱的 真的有几点建议
Sweetie? Really do with some advice.
-是吗  -听着 我不...
- Yeah? - So, look, I don't...
我不想把你卷进来 但是
I don't wanna get you into this, but, um,
比尔在交接时告诉我
well, Bill told me, as part of the handover,
一些"尸体"埋藏的地点
where some of the bodies were buried.
而且 它们埋得不算太好
And, uh, they're not very well-buried bodies,
并且它们都并不算是"尸体"...
and they're not really even bodies, they're...
差不多是僵尸
kind of zombies?
它们随时准备起死回生
They're ready to rise up from the dead at any moment
然后杀了我
and kill me.
我在担心如果... 发生那种事
I'm worried that if... if it does come out,
而且差不多... 一定会发生
and it's sort of... it's kind of bound to come out,
还是发生在我掌权的时候 我就死定了
and it's while I'm in charge, I'm dead,
因为我知道 却什么都没做
because I know, and I'm not doing anything.
但如果硬要我做的话 我必须做点什么
But if I do do something, I've gotta, you know, do something.
-对  -而且我很想
- Right. - And I'd like to,
不是... 显然不是背黑锅
you know, not... obviously not carry the can,
但是做正确的事
but maybe do the right thing.
好的
Ok.
那什么是正确的事
And what is the right thing?
那个 我在想...
Well, what I'm thinking...
举行记者招待会
is a press conference.
-是吗  -是的 然后告诉...
- Oh? OK. - Yeah. And tell...
把大家叫都来 告诉所有高层执行官和律师们
Get everybody in, tell all the top execs and the law guys,
然后咱们公开
and we go public.
公开调查 在日光下消消毒
Open investigation, disinfectant of sunlight,
我们就能将坏死部分
and, you know, we pin the rap
从这批顽皮的坏苹果上挤出去
on a tight group of naughty, rotten apples.
好的
Oh. OK.
听起来蛮勇敢的
Well, that sounds brave.
是的 说得对 听起来不错吗
Yes. Right. Is that good?
抱歉 咱们能再理一遍吗
I'm sorry, can we circle back?
我需要... 接一下乔伊丝的电话
I just... I gotta take this from Joyce.
啥事
Yeah?
听着 我尽力了
Look, I did what I can.
情况是按序演变的
It's dropping down the running order.
但长此以往下去 你得问问自己
But long-term, you gotta ask yourself,
你丈夫肮脏的粉菊花
will your husband's dirty pink asshole
跟宾夕法尼亚大道上那所美丽的白房子配吗
go nicely with that lovely white house on Pennsylvania Avenue?
招手啊 罗曼
Wave, Roman!
等我来
Wait for me.
谢谢你
Thank you.
-等等 等下 等一下  -我很好
- Wait, wait, wait. - I'm OK.
好了 好吧
All right. OK.
你还好吗
You're OK?
我觉得我坚持不下来
I don't think I can do this.
你可以的
Yes, you can.
进去闪瞎他们狗眼
Vas-y and fuck them.
好的 我们走
OK. Let's go.
慢着 给我慢着
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
打扰一下
Excuse me!
这是什么鬼东西
OK, what the hell is this?
叉子吗
Uh, fork?
叉子应该这样放置
Forks are to be placed thusly.
他们在达科他州度假牧场才是这么摆的
This is how they do it at a Dakota dude ranch.
我们在罗伊慈善晚宴是这么摆的
This is how we do it at the RECNY ball.
现在请回去检查每个叉子
Now, please go check every other fork.
难以置信
It's unbelievable.
为什么大家都站在屋子那边
Now, why is everyone standing on this side of the room?
屋子都要倾斜了
The room is growing lopsided.
-我们去赶他们  -什么
- Let's lead them. - What?
像赶羊一样 威拉 我们像羊一样去赶他们
Like sheep, Willa, let's lead them like sheep.
走这边然后把他们圈起来 圈到这边来 好吗
Go around this way and corral them. Corral them this way, OK?
-我走那边  -好的 好的
- I'm gonna go this way. - OK. OK.
大家好
Hello! Everyone!
-大家好呀  -来吧 各位
- Everyone! Hi! - Come on, everybody,
很抱歉打扰了 你们都美极了
I'm sorry to interrupt, you all look fabulous,
我只想说如果你们
I just want to say if you're
在那边找不到饮品
having trouble getting a drink over there,
这边也有同样的吧台...
identical bar over here...
请大家挪到这边来
If you could just go to this side.
享受这个空间 有好几英亩呢 好好享受
Enjoy the space, there's acres of it. So have a good time.
招牌鸡尾酒 太前卫了
The signature cocktail? Too avant-garde.
服务生们在不停堵塞通道
The servers are creating bottlenecks.
他们还在金酒里放香蒜酱... 简直是灾难
They put pesto in the gin... it's a disaster.
要流动起来 斯蒂芬妮
There's no flow, Stephanie.
这晚宴要凝固住了... 没有流动 懂吗
The evening is congealing... there is no flow. OK?
...马克·莫里斯 是的 我爸的第一任妻子
...Mark Morris, yeah, so my dad's first wife
认为她应该清空贫民窟
thought she was gonna, you know, empty the ghettos
一开始的时候就让大家都去跳芭蕾
and get everyone into ballet when they started this thing.
-是吗  -太屈尊附就了
- Yeah. - So patronizing.
你要喝什么
What are you drinking?
白葡萄酒
Uh, a white wine.
能来杯白葡萄酒吗
Can we get a white wine?
有几个孩子进入了纽约城市芭蕾舞团
A couple of the kids who got into New York City Ballet
现在都还在寄圣诞节贺卡
still send us cards at Christmas,
因为她这样很友善啥的吧
because that's nice or whatever.
当然 这很好
No, it's nice.
对 这是...
Yeah. It's, uh...
有点蠢 但还挺酷的
it's dumb, but it's cool.
能来杯比特酒兑苏打水吗
Can I have a bitters and soda?
我其实对上台讲话有点紧张
I'm actually kind of nervous about the speech.
-是吗  -是啊
- Are you? - Yeah.
也许你能... 给我点指导
Maybe you can, uh, give me some pointers.
毕竟你是咱们电视台的专家
You're the ATN pro, actually.
好的 很好
Good, good.
会不会太讽刺了
Is that too wry?
要是这样说我们的业绩 会不会太扎心
About our good works? Is that, like, snitty?
不过全篇都是
Uh, well, there's all this,
整整三页都是
like, three pages of, you know,
关于你 关于家族 还有很棒的业绩 高尚品格
about you and the family, and the good works, and the big hearts,
连绵不绝
and on and on and on.
打断你下 但我没要你的评论轨
Excusing you, but I didn't ask for editorial comment.
现在到肯德尔的部分了 好吧
Now it's into Kendall, OK,
他就都是巴拉巴拉的废话
and he's all blah blah blah.
等下 伙计 这是什么
Hold on, pal. What is this?
倒回去些 这是什么
Roll that back. What is that?
什么
What?
-"洛根的惊喜退休宣言"  -对
- "Surprise Logan retirement announcement." - Uh, yeah.
这条刚加进来 他说会即兴来一段
That came through late. He said he'd just wing it.
好的
Ok.
邦德先生
Mr. Bond.
我一直在等你呢 你还好吗
I've been expecting you. How are ya?
你坐哪里 老兄
Where are you sitting, man?
地下室吗
In the basement?
紧挨着垃圾箱
Out by the dumpsters?
也许... 我们可以换一下
Maybe you... do you want to trade?
你可能会遇到一个有钱的寡妇
Maybe you'll meet a wealthy widow
然后用你可怜兮兮的眼神勾引她
and you can seduce her with your sad eyes.
她就会养宠物一样把你养在富人区
She can keep you as a pet in Westchester.
-你们好  -你好
- Hi, guys. - Hey.
-你今晚很帅  -你也很美
- You look nice this evening. - As do you.
谢谢 那么 汤姆
Thank you. So, Tom,
我听说你要考虑开个小型记者会
I hear you're thinking about holding a little press conference?
-你知道了  -我什么都不知道
- You know about that? - I don't know anything.
好吧 我就是觉得
Right. I just think it's the
-这是应该做的事...  -汤姆 你必须闭上嘴
- best thing to do... - Tom, you need to shut up.
这可不是什么良心发现大声疾呼的好时机
This isn't the time to get your conscience out and shout,
"喂 大家看看我 我不会说谎
"Hey, look at me! I cannot tell a lie!
我是个好男孩 看看我的小丁丁"
I'm a good little boy, look at my ding-dong."
好吧 我觉得你对我的描述有失公正...
OK, I don't think that's a fair characterization of what I'm...
你听说过"罪孽蛋糕处理者"吗
Have you ever heard of the Sin Cake Eater?
-没听过  -处理者会到葬礼上
- No. - He would come to the funeral
然后吃掉所有的
and he would eat all the
摆在尸体上的罪孽蛋糕...
little cakes they laid out on the corpse...
他会把所有罪孽都吃掉
he ate up all the sins.
你知道吗 罪孽蛋糕处理者的工资超高
And you know what? The Sin Cake Eater was very well paid.
供需不断
And so long as there was
他死后立即有人补位
another one who came along after he died,
一切运转良好
it all worked out.
所以 虽然这不是最好的工作
So, this may not be the best situation,
但更难的工作有的是 这些罪孽蛋糕也有的是
but there are harder jobs, and you get a fuckload of cake.
我能不能请问下你从哪儿知道的
Can I ask you where you heard about this, please?
汤姆 现在告诉你这些很艰难
Tom, it's tough to have to tell you like this,
但我其实跟你老妈有性关系
but I'm in a sexual relationship with your mother.
她说梦话说漏了
She talks in her sleep.
打扰了
Excuse me.
晚上好 老爹 你好吗
Hey. Hey, Pa, how ya doin'?
... 我想跟你确认个事
...Just wanted to check in on something.
我想确认下你知不知道肯德尔今晚
Just wanted to check that you're aware of Kendall announcing
宣布你要退休的事
your retirement this evening?
我相信你已经知道了
I mean, I'm sure you were,
就是想再三确认下
but I just wanted to triple-check.
-什么  -是啊 难道不是吗
- What? - Yeah. Is that right?
-不是 -不是吗
- No. - No?
是个失误吗 因为肯德尔要说这事
Is it a mistake? Because Kendall's gonna say it.
已经在提词器上了
It's on the teleprompter.
计划有变了
There's been a change of plan.
肯德尔不会上台讲话
Kendall's not speaking.
我会
I am.
好吧 好的
OK, good.
晚上好 女士们先生们
Good evening, ladies and gentlemen.
我是主持人 马克·雷文海德
I'm your host, Mark Ravenhead,
欢迎大家来到罗伊慈善晚宴
and welcome to the RECNY ball.
黄油太冰了
The butter's too cold!
The butter is too cold!
黄油都被毁了 你们这群卑鄙小人 你们毁了它
The butter's all fucked! You're fuckwads and you fucked it!
-就在我们说话的此刻 餐前面包都被毁了  -康纳
- There's dinner rolls ripping out there as we speak! - Connor!
-康纳  -我就是个笑柄
- Connor. - I am a laughingstock!
服务很多人的时候总会有些问题
There are always issues when you serve this many people,
可我觉得 整体来说
but I think, on the whole,
晚会进行得很好
it's going very well.
自鸣得意 你被炒了
Complacent! You're fired!
你们都被炒了 蠢货
You're all fired! Idiots!
简直他妈的不敢相信 被一群低能环绕
Can't fuckin' believe it. Surrounded by imbeciles!
你 跟我来一下 跟我来
Hey. Come with me. Come with me.
快来
Come on.
-你个恶心的混合肉块  -你好 汤...汤姆
- You lump of fucking turducken. - Hi, T-Tom.
-你去告密了  -什么
- Did you squeal? - What?
你是不是出卖我了 猪头
Did you bitch me out, pig man?
-什么事... -你走漏了我要开新闻发布会的风声
- As in... - You bleated about the fuckin' press conference.
-没有  -你当然有
- No! - Yes, you did.
-不 我没有  -你肯定有
- No, I did not! - Yes, you did,
你这坨恶心的狗屎
you filthy piece of shit.
我就该把你拽进后厨
I ought to drag you into the kitchens
看着他们把你煮熟直到你...
and have them boil you until you're s...
天啊 你居然碰我 格雷格
My God, you just touch me, Greg?
汤姆 很抱... 但你口水都喷到我了...
Tom, I'm sor... Your spittle was actually, like...
棒极了 我们现在该怎么做
This is extraordinary. What are we gonna do about this?
这种侮辱还要继续发展吗
Are these assaults going to be ongoing?
-没有  -你是说没告诉别人吗
- No! - You tell me you didn't do it?
我保证 向上帝发誓
I promise, I swear to God!
那他妈到底是谁说漏的 格雷格
Then who the fuck did, then, Greg?
因为我只告诉了你
Because I only told you.
相信我 老兄...
Believe me, man...
滚蛋
Fuck off.
...从革新网络广播
...revolutionizing Internet radio
到帮助当地小朋友们
to his work with local children.
女士们先生们 掌声欢迎朱诺·赫南德兹
Ladies and gentlemen, please welcome Juno Hernandez!
老爸
Hey, Dad.
我不想在背后说肯德尔的坏话...
Um, so I don't want to shit-talk Kendall, uh...
说他不是这块料...
he ain't up to the job...
但我觉得我能代表所有人对你说
but, uh, I think I speak for everyone here
看到你回归真的很高兴
when I say it's great to see you back.
谢谢你 儿子
Ah, thank you, son.
就是有件事
But one thing, um,
我也不是很在意
and I don't mind, it's fine,
我想问的是弗兰克现在是我的什么
but I do want to say that Frank is what to me, now?
他是副总
He's vice-chairman,
你是总顾问
and you're general advisor.
为什么这么安排
And why is that?
公园的数据现在是多少
What's the situation with the park numbers?
公园数据
Park numbers?
入园数很高
Attendances are good,
但去年入住的客房数却下降了
but the occupied room nights are down on last year.
我只在给汤姆时间让他能完全
I'm just waiting for Tom to get his feet, like,
适应新的位置
fully under the table.
说真的 那家伙老古怪了
The guy is a flake, is actually the truth of it,
交给我 我会处理的
but I'm on it. I'm on it.
你什么时候回公司
When are you coming back in again?
你要听得进弗兰克的谏言
You need to soak up Frank's experience.
好吧 那是什么意思
OK, but what does that mean?
意思就是他怎么说你就怎么做
It means do what he fuckin' tells ya.
很抱歉黄油出了问题
So sorry about the butter, guys.
黄油出问题了吗
There was a problem with the butter?
没解冻
Frozen.
今晚我们支持各位发消息
So remember, texting is encouraged tonight.
千万别发黄色消息
Please, no sexting,
单纯发消息是可以的...
uh, but texting is fine...
州长
Governor.
现在开始募款
Let's get those numbers in.
我想在屏幕上看到所有人的名字
I want to see everybody's name up on that screen,
我谨代表出席晚会的各位
and on behalf of everyone here at RECNY,
向捐款的爱心人士致以谢意
thank you for your donation.
别走
Hold on.
谢谢
Thaaaank you.
你别动
You stick around.
不好意思 我打扰二位了吗
Oh, I'm sorry, am I interrupting something?
你要是这么喜欢她
If you like her so much,
干嘛不他妈问她要电话
why don't you just ask for her fuckin' number?
小罗
Rome.
你肯定很想要 对吗
I mean you clearly want to, right?
格蕾丝 你愿意把手机号给这个人吗
Grace, would you like to give this man your number?
当然 我愿意给他电话
Yeah. I'd like to give him my number.
那你干嘛还不问她要
Why don't you ask for her number, then?
你能告诉我手机号吗
Can I get your number?
能给我支笔吗
Can I have a pen, please?
对嘛 就是这样 这才像样
Oh, OK. Here we go. Yeah. It's happenin'.
唾手可得
That's handy.
还真是她的号码
That's actually her number.
等等 等等
Wait, wait, wait.
请再拿瓶酒过来 谢谢
And fetch another bottle, please. Thank you.
布莱恩 谢谢 弗里茨 谢谢 见到你们很高兴
Thanks, Brian. Thanks, Fritz. Good to see you.
-干得不错 老哥  -什么意思
- Nice work, bro. - What do you mean?
干明星呀
You know, fuckin' the talent.
-别这样  -我不介意的
- Hey. Come on. - No! It's cool It's cool.
你搞泛美 泛美在搞我
You're fuckin' ATN, ATN's fuckin' me--
就他妈瞎几把搞呗
it's a little fucking clusterfuck, yeah?
还好吗
Everything good?
挺好 我玩得很开心
Yes, I'm having a lovely time.
谢谢
Thanks.
很抱歉黄油做成这样
So sorry about the butter.
顺带告诉你一声
And just so you know,
老爸好像马上要上台讲话了
apparently, Dad's going to be doing the speech now,
计划变更得有些迟 应该没问题吧
so late change of plans, I hope that's cool.
-什...  -对 他才说的
- What... - Well, yeah, he just said.
估计这打乱了某人的计划吧
I guess that put a spoke in quite a few wheels, huh?
老康 他身体不行
Con. Con. He's in no fit state.
我得回后台了
Gotta go backstage.
格丽 格丽 能谈谈吗
Uh, Gerri. Gerri. Can we talk?
当然
Sure.
来这儿
Over here.
我爸打算发言
Uh, Dad wants to do the speech.
我不知道
OK. I did not know that.
千真万确 但他一张口 什么都可能会发生
Yeah. When he opens his mouth, anything could come out.
流口水 反犹太
Drool, anti-Semitism,
麻烦得像一串丝巾缠在一起
fucking string of silk handkerchiefs tied together.
他要是在公众前搞砸了
if he fucks up publicly,
我们麻烦就大了
we have a major problem.
-没错  -你得跟他谈谈
- Right. - You need to talk to him.
行 明白了
OK. Got it.
千层面 你知道他们还有千层面吗
Lasagna? Did you know they had some lasagna?
-你要来点吗  -来点吧
- Would you like some? - Oh, yeah.
-你还好吗  -我没事
- You good? - I'm good.
那就好
Great.
祝你今晚好运
Good luck tonight.
一定要演讲成功
Gonna knock it out of the park.
谢谢你
Thank you.
祝你好运
Good luck.
祝你好运[法语]
Bon chance.
好好跳
Best foot forward.
你们可以的
You can do it.
-祝你好运  -谢谢
- Good luck. - Thanks.
-紧张吗  -还好
- Nervous? - Not too bad.
黄油出问题了 不过... 貌似问题不大
I had a thing with the butter, but... seems to be OK.
布什维克: 纽约布鲁克林北部的一个下层中产阶级社区
-你打哪儿来  -布什维克
- Where you from? - Bushwick.
可不是嘛 可不是
Indeed. Yes, indeed.
干得好 辛苦了
Well, wonderful. Great effort.
我是康纳·罗伊
Connor Roy.
很多人也对我有不少成见
People have a lot of preconceptions about me, too.
真的很苦
It's difficult.
我不是说... 当然你也过得很苦
I mean, not... like I'm sure everything is for you,
其实我是这样想的
See, I actually have this idea
社会平等可能会受到
that social equality could be effected
完全废除联邦资助的影响
by a complete eradication of federal support.
像你我这样的人 我们一起
Just people like you and I, doin' it together,
-不畏流言奋战到底...  -到我了
- fighting it out without all the bullshit... - OK, this is me.
演出顺利 我的朋友
Great! Break a leg, my friend.
挺好看的
That was great.
干得漂亮 老康
Good job, Con.
这是我今秋看过最棒的节目
Best event of the fall.
-谢谢你  -真心的
- Thanks, man. - Really.
今晚真是绝了
Hey, terrific evening, huh?
你证明给那些傻逼[囊性纤维]看了 不是吗
You really showed it to those cystic fibrosis fuckheads, huh?
都是为了慈善 不是我 伙计
Well, it's all about the charity. It's not about me, buddy.
-说得对  -好 谢谢
- You're right. - OK, thanks.
各位 大家伙
Hey! Hey, you guys!
你们不会相信外面的人都是怎么说的
You won't believe what people are saying out there.
太棒了 我们完胜
It's amazing! We tore it up.
我们成功了 晚会队得分
We nailed it, man! Score, team RECNY!
你们屌爆了 兄弟们 你们屌爆 屌爆 屌爆了
You're awesome, dude. You're awesome, awesome, awesome.
我爱死你们了
I love you so much. Everyone,
你们真棒 我爱死你们了
you're amazing and I love you so much.
斯蒂芬妮 我的爱 来抱一个
Stephanie, my rock! Come on, bring it.
商业大亨 慈善家
Business mogul, philanthropist,
他的名字印在我的每一张支票上...
and guy whose name is on all of my checks...
女士们先生们
ladies and gentlemen,
我非常荣幸
it is my profound pleasure
在这个喜庆的场合向各位介绍...
to introduce to you, on this most auspicious of occasions...
一位扭转了广告魅力的巨人
in a change to advertised attractions,
一位伟人 一代传奇...
the man, the legend...
洛根·罗伊
Logan Roy!
吓我一跳 我还以为咱们有暖场表演呢
Ooh. Elvis. I thought we were getting a supporting act.
坚持
Keep going.
走到丹身边
Just get to Dan
假装你在说话
and pretend you're talking.
现在有估价四百亿的市值
There's a $40 billion market cap
等着看他是否能撑过来
waiting to see if he makes it.
如果他崩溃 我就会损失好几套房子
If he falls, I'm gonna lose one of my several houses,
然后你就得给我赔
and you're gonna pay for the next one.
天呐 他真的快使出吃奶的劲了
My God, he's really milking the walk.
就快到了 加油
Nearly there. Come on.
谢谢...
Thank you. Um...
...晚上好
uh... evening.
首先 我
First, I'd, uh,
我想谢谢我的妻子 玛西娅...
I'd like to thank my wife, Marcia, for, uh...
谢谢她照料我
everything.
谢谢
Thank you.
还要谢谢
Uh, thanks,
谢谢大家的光临
thanks to you all for coming,
谢谢那些支持我的人
and thanks to those who have supported me
在我近来出现
during my recent
无厘头的健康问题时
health nonsense.
小伤风
Head cold.
没错 对 就是这样
Yeah, uh, yeah, that's, uh, yeah.
那么...
So...
分享一些私人消息
personal n-news.
某人在我住院期间
Someone took advantage
趁着我身体不适
of me being in the hospital,
向...
to...
我的女儿...
propose...
求婚了
to my daughter.
我想借此机会
So I'd like to take this opportunity
欢迎她的未婚夫 汤姆·威姆士丹加入家族
to welcome her fiancé, Tom Wamsgans, to the family.
欢迎加入家族 汤姆
Welcome to the family, Tom.
孩子们相互支持
It's so, so important
相互鼓励真的非常重要
that children are supported and encouraged.
而且...
And, uh...
我所做的一切
everything I've done,
都是为了我的孩子们
I've done for my children.
所以看到他们
And I'm proud of the way
在我欠佳期间齐心协力
that they've pulled together
我深感自豪
during my issue.
尤其是
And, in particular,
我的儿子... 肯德尔
my son... Kendall.
干得好 肯
Well done, Ken.
现在
And now
今晚最后一份声明
for one last announcement of the night.
我正式宣布...
I'm officially announcing...
...我回归了
...I'm back.
信不信由你 我回归了
You better believe, I'm back.
全天候...
Full-time...
犹如涅槃
better than ever.
谢谢大家
Thank you.
太好了
All right!
谢谢大家
Thank you!
-赶紧带我走  -掌声献给洛根·罗伊
- Get me out of here. - Logan Roy, everybody!
"很棒的"讲话 干得好 老爸
Yeah, nice one. Way to go, Dad.
你为什么要这样
Why would you do that? Huh?
我看穿你了
I see you.
你的伎俩被我戳穿了 儿子 以后别想再这么对我
I spied you fuckin' out, son. Don't ever do that to me again.
我不知道你在说啥
I have no idea what you're talking about.
你想甩掉我 就像干掉路边的一只狗
Retire me, shoot me like a dog in the street.
我听说你讲话的内容了
I heard about your little speech.
什么讲话 那本来
My speech? I was gonna do
就是一个调侃你永远都不会退休的笑话
one fuckin' joke about how you'd never retire.
胡说八道
Bullshit!
为什么你不直接跟我谈
Why didn't you just talk to me?
滚蛋
Fuck off.
好了 老爸 没事的
OK, OK. Pa. You're all right.
谢了 马克
OK. Thanks, Mark.
坐这 慢点 慢点
Here. Easy, easy. Yeah.
你还好吗
You OK?
挺好 是你啊 康纳
Yeah. Oh! Hey, Connor.
你今晚做得很棒
You did well tonight.
我真的很为你骄傲
I'm really, really proud of you.
我不能再听从您的命令了 爸
I can no longer obey, Dad.
"我已尝到命令的滋味 不能拱手相让"
"I have tasted command, and I cannot give it up."
这是一位名叫拿·波拿巴的炮兵学员说的
A certain artillery cadet by the name of N. Bonaparte.
你还好吗
Are you OK?
-咱们走吧  -好 走吧
- Let's go. - OK, let's go.
行了
Yeah. OK.
晚安 干得不错
Good night. Good job.
谢谢您
Thank you.
那啥 安娜...
You know, look, Anna...
我能问一句...
can I just ask...
有什么... 你不满意的吗
is there something... going on here?
-什么呢  -不知道
- As in? - I don't know,
就是气氛吧 我说什么话冒犯到你了吗
is there an atmosphere? Did I say something to offend you?
今晚非常棒
This has been a lovely evening.
我很开心能来
I was so happy to come.
那是我有病咯
So, am I crazy?
我感觉自己在跟应用程序约会
I feel like I'm on a date with an app.
感觉隔着无形的泡泡纸
Like there's this invisible bubble wrap.
其实...
Look, um...
说句不该说的
off the record,
不该说的
off off,
你是个很好的... 人
you seem like a nice... guy.
谢谢
Thank you.
伊娃让我来陪你
Eva told me to come.
她请求你 对吧
Asked. I mean,
我请求她来请求你
I asked her to just, you know, ask your people.
都一样
It's fine.
我刚认识个男的
I'm just seeing someone,
但你... 你是老板
but y-you... you're the boss.
不 不是这样的 我不是那种人
No. No, no, no. I'm-- I'm not that guy.
当然 你不是 我...
Yeah, sure. No. I'm...
好吧 其实你就是那种人 此时此刻
But actually, you are the guy. Right now.
她是怎么说的 伊娃
What did she say? Eva?
没什么
Nothing.
拜托 求你了
Come on. Please, just--
她说要确保你过得很开心
To make sure that you had a really good time.
她在搞笑吗
Was she joking?
当然
Sure.
好吧 我更希望你不要说出去
OK, uh, and I'd prefer it if you didn't say anything.
但我想说
Well, uh, I think I should.
请不要说
Please don't.
好吧 不说
OK. Sure.
拜托 老哥 这是咱家的慈善晚宴
Hey, come on, man. This is our charity.
一客多少钱来着 最不济也能买次口活吧
How much a plate? You gotta get at least a blow job.
法律这么规定的
That's the law.
法律没这么规定过
That's not the law.
那至少是道德准则
Well, it's the ethical code, then,
我不想这么说
and I hate to say this,
但她表现得非常不道德
but she's behaved rather unethically here.
我过得很开心
Had a really good time.
好孩子 这步走得很机智
Good kid. Smart move.
继续保持
Keep talking.
乐意为您效劳 女士
I aim to please, ma'am.
你叫他打过来没
Did you tell him to call?
别吵醒他
Don't wake him up.
请关上门
Please close the door.
继续开
Keep driving.
我想让他多睡会儿
I want him to sleep.
THE SUB-MAN
关注新浪微博
@FIX字幕侠